♪ I leave gold on the floor
Wherever I go ♪
♪ I'm killing it
I'm stealing the show ♪
♪ Words fall out my mouth
And they break the door ♪
I like dating a girl that
doesn't watch football
and then I can make her a fan of my team.
Works great, like Mary is a Redskins fan.
Mary, who is your favorite football team?
[Mary] Redskins.
Yes. Fucking love you, baby.
-[Mary] That's why you're my bestie.
-[Jason] Uh!
-[Mary] One of my besties.
-[Jason laughing]
Sorry, I ate pizza last night.
What about your second favorite?
You have a second favorite?
[Mary] The Raiders.
Hey, can I talk to you for a sec
about Adnan?
-Yeah.
-[Davina] Okay, let's talk about it.
[Davina] Jay, do you have a minute?
-Yeah, sure.
-[Davina] Okay, cool.
[Davina clears throat]
[Davina] So, I know we kind of talked
about Adnan and his properties.
Very special house in Beverly Hills.
So, I saw that house that they're talking
about right now, Davina's listing,
and it's gorgeous.
-[Maya] What do you think it is worth?
-I don't...
[Christine] It is one of the most
well done houses I have seen,
I told her, ever,
and I'm not making that up.
It is so impeccably...
-Everything is perfect.
-[Maya] Hold on.
It's so meticulous, it's great.
No, go ahead.
Christian, I'm actually talking to your
fiancé here, she likes this house.
[Christine] I wish.
Listen, it's a dope house.
It's a great listing.
I know.
It's just that does it do more damage to
have a listing like that, we don't sell?
A pocket listing, I think, could...
-We don't have to spend any marketing.
-Sure.
We can make phone calls
and bring clients in.
Then it's not going to be like
announced to the world.
We can send a private email
or phone calls to people.
We don't have to spend marketing money.
So it's not as...
Here's my question,
I'm thinking to myself.
Do I want to send that property
to clients or is it embarrassing?
A pocket listing is interesting.
It does reduce our marketing expenses,
but I'm also concerned about
how a pocket listing,
overpriced like this, could affect
the reputation of the brokerage.
[Jason] We spent a lot of time
building a reputation
of a brokerage
that has well-priced listings.
What are you guys whispering about?
About Jason giving Davina a hard time
about the listing.
-I mean it's probably overpriced.
-It will be like the biggest listing...
that anyone in the office has ever had.
-Is that what they are talking about?
-Yeah.
He doesn't want her to waste her time.
But you just never know.
I mean, you can waste your time
with a two million dollar listing
just as easily as you can
with an 80 million dollar listing.
[Maya] Exactly.
-[Christine] Price is relative.
-Or with a lease.
If she doesn't take it
and what if someone else swoops in,
gets it and then sells it?
What's she gonna say,
"Oh no, I don't wanna to take it"?
She can tell the client, sure I think it's
a bit overpriced, but I'm happy to try.
I think Jason is not only
being unreasonable,
but a little harsh with Davina.
If this was Mary's listing,
he would be like,
"Yeah babe, get it babe, crush it babe,
yeah babe, I got a client for you,
let's sell it together, babe!
I got this for you!"
But that's just Mary so...
She shouldn't shut this
opportunity down at all.
-She should definitely take it.
-I agree.
How long of a listing
is he going to give you?
[Davina] It's a three-month listing.
-I think he wants to see effort--
-So pointless.
He knows the price is high.
What's gonna happen,
we'll have it for three months,
we're not gonna get
a single fucking phone call.
-I know.
-Why would you say that?
What if we tell people, "make offers"?
You know? We call some of the
bigger agents and we say, "bring offers."
I'm just wondering if this fucks up our
chance to get his other stuff, because...
No, I think he might do it simultaneously.
For sure, Laurel Way,
he's like, "Let's do it right now."
[Christine] Taking this listing
is about more than
having a huge expensive house to sell.
The owner's a property developer.
He has dozens of other properties he can
give to the Oppenheim Group to sell.
It's a really big deal.
[Davina] I have to try.
-So, I'm going to do it.
-I...
-I think that we can figure it out.
-Well, we have to agree on this.
You can't just do it.
I'm gonna make a coffee.
[Brett] Yo, let's talk about this.
She might get 50-55, in which case
it's probably worth a pitch because:
A. She can get clients, from it.
B. She might get another listing.
C. There's a chance that it sells.
-He's a pretty awesome potential client.
-Yeah.
I am not trying to be a dick about it.
I'm also not trying to waste
my time and my clients' time.
[Brett] That's my mentality.
I think it's fair.
Well, fuck it, we'll let her do it.
I'm gonna let her do it, all right.
-I mean, it's a pocket listing, so...
-Yeah.
-With no marketing dollars.
Three months, I guess,
what can go wrong? Right?
Uh... I do want to congratulate Davina
on a 75 million dollar pocket listing,
which is the largest
in the office right now.
No pressure, guys.
Call everyone you know!
Ask everyone you know!
You guys, we should all say a prayer
for Davina right now.
♪ Everybody wanna be like us
Everybody wanna be like us ♪
♪ Everybody wanna talk like us
L-L-L-L-Like us ♪
♪ Everybody wanna step with us
But you can't step with us ♪
-[Heather] Such dorks!
-[Christine] Like Charlie's Angel's!
-We are matching and cute today.
-I love it.
[Heather] Oh, man.
-How cute is this place?
-[cashier] Hi.
[Heather] Hi. How are you?
Uh... Any dessert?
You're a snack already.
What else could I need?
I think I'm going to do
an extra hot chai tea latte.
Can I have a latte with macadamia milk?
I'm going to try that, and hazelnut, yeah.
-I want that.
-With extra foam.
-You can try mine. Just a sip.
-Is it coffee, though?
-Yeah.
-Can you bitches shut up so I can order?
♪ Everybody wanna sit with us
But you can't sit with us ♪
♪ Everybody wanna be like us
Everybody... wanna... be like... us ♪
-Warming up.
-It is warming up.
I've been getting these little
stress rashes on my forehead.
[Davina] Oh really?
-From what?
-I don't... Stress.
[Christine] The office stressed her out.
I missed that whole thing.
How did it even start?
Amanza, first she said...
She gave me a compliment.
She's like, "Oh, that's..."
She turned around real quick!
First, she was sweet.
Like, "It's great that you did that.
Like, me being a mom.
My ex's girlfriends never did that,
so that's great that you did that.
I would respect that."
And we were like, "Oh, right. I see now."
-That makes sense, why they were talking.
-And I went, "Thank you, honey."
Then she's like, "But I do think
you guys are moving too fast."
[Amanza] It terrifies me how fast
you've met those kids.
[Heather] Why?
[Amanza] When and if something
doesn't work out, their hearts are--
Excuse me! When what doesn't work out?
If I thought that you were going to be
this angry at me for saying it,
-I would've kept my mouth shut.
-I appreciate that.
Well, you don't.
-No, I actually don't.
-Then don't say you do.
I think people should mind
their own business. [scoffs]
First of all, I don't give a shit
what you think how fast
I'm moving in my relationship or not.
-I really don't care what you think.
-Yeah.
I was in shock.
I was just sitting there like...
Whatever she went through,
I'm sorry about that.
But don't project your issues
on my life and my relationship.
I don't need someone's opinion
that doesn't know who I am.
Did you ask her?
No, it was unsolicited, right?
Unsolicited and it's rude.
It's very, very rude.
So, it went from her and I
could have maybe a friendship,
but now I am going to have my guard up
with someone like that because
you have now talked negative about me
and the man that I love and his children.
-Yeah.
-This is a huge deal for me and Tarek.
He is introducing his children to me.
We're incorporating our families
and our lives together.
-They are now going to be my little cubs.
-[Davina groans]
-[Davina] Yeah.
-It was judgmental and evil.
I don't know how I feel about being around
her, if I even want to be around her.
[Davina] Are you going to her party?
I don't know, I guess if I don't go,
they're gonna probably talk about...
I don't know.
♪ Sticks and stones may break my bones ♪
♪ But words can never hurt me ♪
♪ I'mma grab your attention
With the way I get mine ♪
♪ Take you to a new dimension
Won't believe your own eyes ♪
♪ I'm better than ever... ♪
[Amanza] I have these awesome clients,
from my design work
and they have
an insane beach house in Malibu
that they never use.
Which works great for us, because they
have offered it up to the entire office
to come for the day,
to hang out, have a beach day
and blow off some steam.
Hey, sexy!
-Oh my God, look at you.
-[Amanza] Hi!
You look adorable.
-How are you?
-Just playing with my balls. [laughing]
[Mary chuckles]
-[Chrishell] So cute.
-Do you want a drink?
-Hey, girls.
-Hey!
-How are you?
-Hey, guys.
Hey, thanks for having us here.
[Christine laughing]
-Hi, guys.
-You good?
Oh my gosh.
Hi, babe!
How are you? I'll get to you eventually.
-Slowly. Sideways.
-That is impressive.
[cork pops]
[Jason] Get some ice for that rosé.
[Romain] Sorry.
[Brett] If you don't catch this,
you're on burger duty.
Oh! What is wrong with you two?
Hey, so is Heather coming?
I think she's going to, but I really don't
know. I haven't talked to her today.
I don't know if she's still upset with me.
I don't know if she's coming.
I haven't heard from her.
The only thing that I'm slightly nervous
about is this Heather situation because
we haven't really talked about it
since our little run-in in the office.
So... I don't know,
we'll see if she shows up and hopefully
if she does, it'll go smoothly.
Sometimes, things fester
if you don't just like...
Yeah, that's how I feel. I just want to
talk about it and get it over with, but...
I don't know.
[Chrishell] Is our sun...
Oh my God, that scared me!
[Maya] Who is that mermaid?
[Amanza] You look like
you have on a onesie.
[all laughing]
I don't want to hear about onesie.
Do you say "onesie" or "onzie"?
How do you say that?
-Onesie.
-Onesie?
I'll refill this. Does anyone want
more to drink real quick?
[Maya] You think...
Damn, I need sunglasses here, you know?
I'm going to strip down real quick.
-I'm just so hot. Sorry.
-[Maya] I like that suit.
Thank you. Isn't it slutty?
-It is. I'm sure Christian likes it.
-Maya.
Argh!
Tom Brady or not?
-[Brett] You catch better than Romain.
-I break a nail,
I am invoicing Brett this time.
Hey!
-[Jason] Three hours late.
-[Christine] Hi, babe!
Heather just got here.
-[Mary] Who?
-Heather.
-Fashionably late.
-Alright, what is fashionably late?
Had to get my hair braided.
-Is she going to be okay?
-I don't know.
-Hi, guys.
-[Maya] Hey, Heather! Catch!
[Chrishell] How are you, babe?
Come sit down.
Are you talking with Heather?
Are you guys talking,
like you guys are good?
I think so.
[Amanza] Can I sit here?
Am I in your way?
[Mary] Amanza's got some vegan burgers
over there for you.
Oh, amazing.
[Maya] I feel like Amanza is trying
to make peace by bringing the vegan food.
What's up?
Are you trying to make amends?
Yeah, I mean I would like to.
We can talk now.
-[Christine] Do you guys want privacy?
-I want to say... No.
You know, I honestly was coming
from... my heart.
I just felt so passionately about the
situation because I'm going through it,
so it was kind of a knee-jerk reaction,
and so I apologize
if it came off insensitive.
That was not my intention at all.
Maybe you meant a different way,
but you said what you said, so...
I understand you're trying to be
protective or whatever.
You've gone through it.
But I don't go into
a relationship with negativity.
I feel there's a difference
between negativity and precaution,
and I think that nobody
goes into a relationship
thinking it is not going to work.
With kids, it's just,
you might not want to be cautious
or you might not want to feel negative,
but you have to.
But I don't need you to be concerned
about my situation.
You understand?
You can be concerned with your situation
and whoever else you want
to be concerned with,
but you don't know me that well.
You don't know Tarek.
You don't know our relationship
with the children or anything else.
So, it doesn't matter
if we've been together a month,
six months, two years or three,
we felt it was ready.
So, you know, we're going with it.
[Chrishell] I am a stepmom.
My husband was married before
and he has a daughter.
Hopefully Heather slows down a little bit
because it's tough.
You know, there's not a rule book.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what else to say.
I am sorry. I don't like drama.
I don't like negativity.
I like you,
not that you're asking me to like you,
but we have a small group in the office.
I don't want to be, like,
have weirdness. You know?
I hate that it happened.
I wish it didn't.
But I am not going to hold a grudge,
like I said,
now I am going to be a bit more cautious.
I'm sure I'll get past it.
Well, I will too.
I'll be cautious too.
So, it's like, you know...
You guys. If we can get past it,
you guys can get past it.
[Christine] Honestly, the longest grudge
ever right here,
and we nailed that shit.
[indistinct chattering]
Y'all.
[Heather] You look like a stripper
right now.
Like a hot stripper though.
[Christine laughing]
How's the wedding planning going, guys?
The guest list...
So we have cut it in half.
We were gonna have 100-something.
We've got it down to about 60 now.
We have rules on it.
How often we have to talk to them,
how often we hang out with them.
But he's got one that I've been
fighting with him on
-and he's not budging.
-I don't want Davina in my wedding.
-[Chrisehll] Who?
-Davina.
Oh!
Why?
I feel like the way she disrespected me
about the ring, about like,
she said to Chrishell,
"Yeah, she pays everything for him."
You know us and you know
she doesn't pay for me.
I think it was such bullshit.
And she talked shit about the ring
that I bought her at the beginning
because I couldn't afford anything else.
And that's okay.
It doesn't matter about the ring,
it matters about the love.
[Romain] The way she said,
"I would rather have nothing
than a fake diamond."
Like, who the fuck are you?
So that's the point.
I think someone
that disrespects me that much,
do not think to come to my wedding.
Like, no way.
[Romain] The meaning of getting engaged
is love and not about the material.
I could have put a rubber band
on her finger
and she should be happy for her.
So, for Davina to make that comment
about the fake diamond,
it was rude and disrespectful.
I don't think if you are a friend,
you should ever say something like that.
I don't need those persons at my wedding.
Maybe you guys can talk to her
because we all work together.
No, I am stubborn
more than anyone, and I know it.
As soon as I switch, it's done.
[Christine] Don't you think it's conflict
to not invite someone
just because of their opinions?
Listen, I don't know,
I say shit all the time and then
I expect to be invited to parties,
so I don't know,
I'm the wrong person to ask, personally.
I don't care. I won't change my mind.
You can't disrespect me
and just come, "Oh, I'm sorry."
"Okay, fine. You can come now."
No, it doesn't work that way.
[Christine] Being privy to this
information is making me uncomfortable.
Davina and I have become really close.
I think Davina's really smart
and I like that she speaks her mind.
I always liked that about her.
I feel like she's real.
She's the only one that doesn't have
fake boobs here, so shit. [laughing]
She's as real as it gets
in this office.
[Romain] I don't want Davina
at my wedding.
Like I said, I won't change my mind.
[Christine] I didn't know
that side of him.
That was a side I have not seen before.
I have not seen Romain be
so shirtless and passionate.
[laughing] No, I've seen him do shirtless,
but I feel like that was a conversation
that Mary and Romain
should have had privately,
and blurting it out to the whole office
is really unfair to Davina.
So, I will do everything to protect her.
[Mary] Everyone swear no one's
saying a word to Davina.
-No.
-[Mary] We obviously need to talk to her.
-[Chrishell] I'm steering clear of that.
-Yeah.
[Mary] But I want it to come from us.
I want to do it out of respect.
-Yeah.
-Seriously.
So, Romain, 100 percent?
-You're really sure about it?
-A thousand percent.
A thousand though?
How about a million?
-She needed to know before all of us.
-Yeah.
It's already too late, but...
I won't say anything, I am going
to respect that if you guys...
[Heather] It's you guys' decision.
You guys handle it.
[Mary] We need to talk to her tomorrow
because I completely agree,
but I've been putting it off,
thinking I can change his mind.
I'm so glad I got married
right before I joined the office.
[laughing] That would have been
too stressful.
♪ Big girls don't scream
Hot like Halloween ♪
♪ Make me feel alive ♪
♪ They damaging the neighborhood ♪
♪ I've been causing way too much
Trouble, trouble ♪
-[Jason] Hey.
-Thanks for coming.
-[Jason] Oh, glad to be here.
-Gonna get a workout coming up this thing.
-Good to see you.
-Hi. Good to see you too.
-Alright, let's do this.
-Alright.
Nice work hustling.
Can't believe you got this
just by running around the Valley.
[Chrishell] I know, I'm a little scrappy.
Hello.
-Hey, how are you doing?
-[Chrishell] Wow!
[Chrishell] This is spectacular.
-[Guy] Nice to see you again.
-Hi, Guy, so good to see you.
This is Jason Oppenheim.
He's my broker I was telling you about.
I'm excited for him to see it.
Thank you for meeting us.
Great, no problem.
[Chrishell] The owner of this property is
a real estate developer.
That means he's constantly looking
for places that he can either renovate
or tear down completely and rebuild,
but still make a profit.
It's really key to get in good
with certain real estate developers
because they can just feed you
business constantly.
[Guy] We'll see
if we can make this happen.
[Chrishell] Do you mind showing us
a little bit around?
-[Guy] Yeah, of course.
-[Jason] This is really nice.
-[Chrishell] You have a basketball court.
-[Guy] Yeah.
[Jason] Yeah, we got a pretty big yard.
[Chrishell] There's a lot at stake
with meeting this real estate developer.
Guy needs to agree to give me the listing,
which I'm hoping he does
because this could really be my chance
to prove to Jason that I can be
successful in the Valley.
So, I'm nervous,
but I really hope that he will see this
as a business match made in heaven.
[Guy] Just the retaining walls alone
took me a year to do.
Really?
I spent as much as it would cost you
almost to build a house.
Just to do these retaining walls
and take out all the dirt.
[Jason] When you bought this,
you didn't have nearly as much flat land.
You pushed everything out then built
these walls to hold the dirt back.
Just one big hill all the way through.
Where we're standing,
we'd be under dirt right now.
That alone took a year.
Just the preparation.
Not the build process.
[Jason] Hopefully,
you got a good deal on the land.
I did. I bought it back in 2012.
2012? You've been working on this
for seven years?
-[Guy] Yes.
-Oh my goodness.
This is a labor of love.
You need it to be in the right hands.
[Guy] It's been seven years.
[Jason] If this was a kid,
it would be in grade school.
It's very lucky that you met us
because we are the best team, I feel.
He dominates.
You already know the brokerage?
Yeah.
I've heard of you guys.
That's why you are here.
You just saved all of us about 15 minutes
of me bragging, so thank you.
[Chrishell] I'd love to check out
more of the house.
-Can we peek around the corner?
-[Guy] Yeah, definitely.
[Chrishell] Yeah, I love
how big and airy this is.
LED lights under each step,
that's a nice finish.
[Guy] This is the master bedroom,
in case you didn't know.
I know it's hard to tell.
I should put signs, right?
[Jason] No, it's pretty impressive. Wow.
-God, look at this closet.
-[Chrishell] Ooh!
-[Jason] Nicely done, Guy.
-[Chrishell] Beautiful.
I love the wood beams.
-I just think it warms up the whole place.
-I agree, it really softens it.
I'm impressed with Chishell's hustle,
and I really want this listing.
It's a gorgeous house.
[Chrishell] Wow, this is so pretty.
I know it's going to take
a lot more to sell this house
because it's more expensive,
but what will make it different with you?
I need to bring an agent
that actually has the buyer.
We're branching out into a new area,
so we want to do that.
We will be able to use your house as the
forefront of our marketing to the Valley.
I like the fact you're going to spend more
than you normally would even on marketing.
It's going to be
a branding opportunity for us
at the same time
we're trying to sell your house.
What would you do different
than a two million dollar house?
Everything. We'll start at the beginning.
Our photography is the best.
We do fashion, daytime,
twilight photography.
Move onto drone photography,
3D virtual tours.
We do 12-page brochures,
instead of booklets,
that we give to every agent
and every prospective buyer.
[Guy] Price is so important.
So... You're not the only brokers.
I've met with other people.
-I'm leaving.
-[Jason] We're not worried.
[Guy] I've met with other brokers.
They've gone over prices with me.
They told me how much they'd like
to market it for. Prices around five...
The important thing is
to take in all the factors.
You've done such a great job with it,
but it is vertical.
Some people are going to want
a little flatter.
I'm hoping that you're thinking
under 800 per square foot.
I was thinking around 4.5.
-What are your thoughts?
-Of course I'd like to get more.
You know? I think it's worth even 5.5
You could put it up.
You know, maybe if you did like
4.595 or something like that,
where it's like...
I just feel like if you put a six on it,
just because of what's in the area,
I don't know...
[Guy] I'm going to put my faith
in you guys and give you the listing.
-Yeah!
-Hope for the best.
You're making a very good decision.
I love this house.
I'm so excited that Guy
gave me this listing.
This could really be the key
to many other listings,
so I am just on cloud nine.
Cloud ten. Is there a cloud ten?
I'm on cloud ten.
[Jason] Let's go to lunch
and figure out strategy.
[Chrishell] Lunch? We have work to do.
That guy, if we do a good job,
will be feeding us important listings.
[Christine] Are you excited?
-So excited to show you.
-My God.
This is where I'm gonna have
my engagement party.
-Can't wait to see it.
-Lisa's such a good planner.
Oh my God. All your parties are epic.
[engine revs loudly]
Okay...
That's how I drive, though.
Such an asshole.
[Christine] Can't wait to show you.
[Christine] Knock knock.
-[Lisa] Hey.
-[Christine] Oh my gosh.
-This is amazing.
-[Lisa] Congratulations.
Thanks, babe. How are you?
Okay, I must see the ring.
-Let's see.
-Oh, yes.
Oh my God.
-[Lisa] Woman.
-[Christine] Isn't it beautiful?
This is my girlfriend Davina.
This is Lisa.
A pleasure.
She plans all my parties. She's the best.
Don't you love this?
Isn't this amazing?
[Christine] I love
the indoor-outdoor vibe.
It's sexy and all the crystals... So...
This will be casual.
Stuff going on like no big deal.
-Like sexual Phantom of the Opera.
-Exactly.
[Christine] I'm thinking
like a zebra here.
-A zebra?
-[Christine] Yeah.
Wait, you're gonna have
a real live zebra?
Yeah, like Britney Spear's music video.
The most beautiful animal in the whole
entire world just like hanging out.
-I just want him to chill.
-[Lisa] Okay.
-And then let's get like fire dancers.
-[Lisa] Love it.
I like the idea of something going on
in the background,
but not full attention to it.
I want, like, Cirque du Soleil performers.
Can we fly them in from Vegas?
-For sure.
-What's your budget for this?
My budget is love, so...
I love that!
-So... casual.
-[Lisa] Okay, great.
I know Christine and there's no way
this party is going to be casual.
It's going to be the exact opposite.
[Davina] This is gonna be really fun.
I think it'll be nice
'cause it'll be intimate.
I just want close family...
-Yeah.
-...close, close friends.
And everyone that I work with, obviously.
I'm so excited for you,
it's going to be awesome.
So, there's something that I want
to talk with you about.
Mm-hmm.
-And...
-Oh my God, what is it?
It's been brought to my attention
in a very, very awkward way.
-So, when we had this beach party...
-Mm-hmm.
...something came up
totally out of left field.
And Romain had mentioned
that he doesn't want you at the wedding.
Oh, wow.
We're all sitting there
like totally stunned.
He basically just said--
-I had no idea he was even upset.
-That's what we all said.
-[Davina] Why?
-I'm just as confused as you are.
It's like Heather doing a math equation.
I'm so fucking confused right now.
I don't know where it came from.
-Wow, okay.
-But he was just...
"Davina does not respect my relationship."
-Blah blah blah blah.
-He said that?
That is crazy.
It hurts my feelings
and honestly it's kind of disrespectful.
Like I wish... At least Mary
should have come to me.
Why can't you come tell me?
Because that takes balls
and we're talking about Mary.
♪ First things first
I'm a sinner ♪
I don't I don't even know what to say.
Let's talk about hypocrisy really quick.
Why does Chrishell get away scot-free
if she was the one
who talked about the prenup?
Asking for a friend.
Not a real friend
because these bitches clearly aren't,
but like asking for anyone.
I'm so sorry to even
have to be telling you this.
I didn't want this to be an Eyes Wide Shut
situation. You needed to know.
♪ I'm wicked as they come ♪
♪ VIP,  I'm a VIP ♪
♪ I said you can get to know me
I'm a VIP ♪
♪ Put you on my level
I want money, I want money ♪
Have you been here, Chrishell?
[Chrishell] I have. I love this place.
It smells so good.
Smells fresh.
Wait, before we sit down,
let's play musical chairs.
Come on, I'm kidding.
[Heather] What?
That is a fun game.
-Can I put my purse here? Who's missing?
-Yeah.
[Maya] Where is Amanza?
[Mary] She, um...
She's been having some issues
with her kids' dad.
They don't really know
what's going on, but...
-It's just weird.
-[Maya] Wow.
My ex-husband and I have been divorced
since my kids were one and two.
For the past seven years, they've spent
a week with Daddy
and a week with Mommy.
And Daddy's a great dad.
He's very... like, present.
But over the past couple of months
stuff really hit the fan, and...
he's basically just off the grid, and...
we don't really know what's going on.
Um...
[crying] I don't have any answers for you.
-[Jason] Way to make lunch somber.
-I know, sorry.
Oh, what's this?
Ooh!
-[Mary] Yummy.
-What is this for?
What are we celebrating?
-There's a lot to celebrate.
-It's a pregnancy test
-to see who doesn't drink.
-[all laughing]
Guys, I think first and foremost, despite
a really turbulent market this year,
despite a lot of other brokerages
having a difficult year,
we are up probably
almost 25 percent this year.
Not only as a broker
are we having our best year ever,
despite, I think, a pretty soft market,
I think everyone here individually
is having their best year.
We're selling more homes,
we have more listings.
We're gonna do over 300 million this year,
which is our best year ever.
380 including Davina's listing.
[Christine laughing]
[Jason] And Chrishell,
your hustle in the Valley,
pounding pavement,
got a five million dollar listing.
[Mary] Yay, that's huge.
[Jason] Really impressive.
Brett... just closed on
a $17.5 million deal in Beverly Hills,
and is in escrow on a $17 million deal.
That's 35 million right there.
Amazing.
-So we're all kicking ass.
-Cheers to that.
-That's really exciting, guys.
-Congrats, you guys.
-[Jason] To family, everyone.
-To family.
So, Mary, have you, um...
Do you have any idea
what venue you're looking into?
Like, what your plans are?
Um...
Kind of.
[Mary] It's just so stressful.
Oh my God, we have seen every type
of venue you could possibly imagine.
We have gone to the beach,
we've gone to vineyards,
we've gone to proper wedding venues,
we've gone to rooftops,
we've gone to hotels...
[Jason] Listen, in a worst-case scenario,
please understand you can use my house
if you need to as a wedding venue.
-Aw!
-[Mary] That's awesome.
Hon, I love you.
I appreciate it. Thank you.
[Maya] Speaking about weddings,
did you tell Davina yet
she's not invited?
I haven't seen her, and I think
it's better to do it in person,
not over the phone and I just feel--
Because everyone knows except her.
Again, no one say anything.
Sorry, not sorry.
I think office dynamics
should come before husband.
[Chrishell] You guys don't know,
you're not in a relationship,
but everybody at this table,
if our man took a stance on something,
I doubt anybody would pick the office
over our husband.
I don't see Davina as "the office."
I see her as a person with feelings
and a human
that we interact with on a daily basis.
Sometimes Christine makes
an effort to piss me off
and sometimes she wins.
But for the most part
I'm able to stay unbothered and...
not give her the time of day.
While all you bitches are figuring out
who you're firing and hiring over there
for all your parties and weddings,
just know that you guys are all invited
to my engagement celebration this weekend.
It's gonna be casual,
just close friends and family.
There's a few surprises.
I'm not going to tell you guys yet,
but it'll be fun.
I don't trust Christine
when she says "casual."
-No, it's "Christine casual."
-No, it is casual.
-What should we wear.
-[Christine] Sexual.
What does that mean?
-[Maya] Victoria Secret?
-Like lingerie... I'm just joking.
[Christine] It'll just be...
-[Brett] It's "Christine casual."
-It'll be "sexual cocktail party."
Just wear like a dress, you know?
-I'm wearing a black dress.
-Like the Oscars.
Like you're going to the Emmy's.
No, I'm just kidding.
The theme's black and red
so I'd love if you wore black or red.
But you don't have to.
You invited Davina, right?
Everyone's invited, so no excuses.
-I'm coming.
-Sounds good.
There's gonna be surprises.
[Chrishell] Is it possible
to coexist with Christine?
I do think it's possible.
I feel like as long as two people
can agree to be professional,
you don't have to be best friends.
Now granted, there are times,
I wonder how much
she was hugged as a child
because sometimes
she can really hit below the belt,
but as far as going to Christine's party,
I feel like I haven't decided yet
and I don't need to right now.
Be there or be square.
-Be there or be square.
-Nice, Maya.
Write that down before you forget it.
It's a good one.
I'm just bored, guys.
[Maya and Mary laughing]
-Wanna sit there?
-Yeah.
-[server] Welcome to The Henry.
-[Mary] Thank you.
Thank you.
I'm gonna do a spicy mezcal margarita.
Spicy mezcal margarita.
Can I try the Pimm's Rye?
Pimm's Rye.
-Some guacamole with chips.
-Guacamole with chips.
-Thank you.
-Thank you. Right.
This is nice,
getting to actually go out with you.
-[Mary] It's been like...
-Two or three months?
Like, our version of a date has been like,
a drink and dinner at the table
trying to plan this stupid wedding.
Are you sure you don't want to elope?
You know it's not gonna
happen like that, so...
-Keep going.
-Keep planning?
-With you helping.
Yeah.
[Mary] We have six weeks
until the wedding. We have guests
flying in from out of town,
and we don't have a venue.
We're running out of time.
I know.
If this wedding...
the location doesn't work out,
Jason has offered his house.
No.
-He just threw it out there, so...
-Thank you so much.
[Mary] Thank you.
I wanted to let you know
because the date is coming up soon.
-But--
-We're still struggling to find...
-I understand.
-...something that's going to work.
-Like.
-This could save us a lot of money.
We could use it for the honeymoon,
and buying a house...
Because this wedding is costing
a lot of money.
I understand, but it's simple.
I'm not going to get married
at the ex's of my future wife.
I mean, there's no fucking way.
-Can we not look at it as my ex-boyfriend?
-No.
-Can we look at it like a friend?
-No babe, I don't care. I understand.
Would you get married
at my ex-girlfriend's house?
I'm not going to get married at Jason's,
your ex-boyfriend. Period.
I feel like I'm going to go insane
planning this wedding.
Romain is being so stubborn.
I don't know how much
more I can take.
Well, okay. It's not just the venue
that's causing me stress.
It's you and this whole Davina issue, too.
This is not making my life much easier,
you know?
Yeah, but I'm not gonna change my mind.
It is what it is.
We're gonna have to talk
to her really soon.
Yeah.
Relax. Oh my God.
You're not around her, and I am.
I'm gonna have to deal
with this afterwards.
I don't want to hurt her feelings.
I really, really don't give a shit
about how she's gonna feel.
Can you please respect the fact
that I have to continue to work with her?
You think too much about the damage,
"What is the damage gonna be?"
I do care about that.
I'll always care about that.
Did she?
It doesn't matter what she did.
To me, it doesn't matter.
Why would you care for someone
that didn't care about you?
You're being so frickin' stubborn.
Yeah, but I have a reason for it.
I have a reason for wanting
to not start drama in the office.
It's pissing me off that you're
only caring about yourself right now
and about your feelings
and about how you were offended.
You don't give a shit that I have to work
with her and be miserable if--
Stop talking about her.
I am getting pissed off at that.
Well, I'm getting pissed off because
you're not taking into consideration--
-I don't care what she's gonna feel.
-You should care how I feel.
You're just being stupid.
[Mary] I've had enough
of this petty drama with everybody.
Romain is turning into
some sort of groom-zilla.
Well, you're going to see her at
-Christine's, um...
-Great.
You're really coming off as a dick,
you know that, right?
We are going to end
this conversation right now
because I'm not gonna get
into this anymore.
No, I don't give a fuck.
♪ If this is love
Then love is danger ♪
♪ Take off my dress with dirty fingers ♪
♪ I must confess we're dirty creatures ♪
♪ Swear you'll never leave me ♪
♪ We're fading now but I believe ♪
♪ Not even God could come between us ♪